<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PollutionControlBoard</string>
    <string name="launch">AirMo.......</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">AirMo</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Username</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in" translatable="false">New User? Click Here to Register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short" translatable="false">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="name">"AIR POLLUTION MONITORING APP"</string>
    <string name="todo">hello</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="search">SEARCH</string>
    <string name="NAME">enter your name</string>

    <string name="share">"Add your idea here"</string>
    <string name="btn10">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="laa">.....feel the Air..</string>

    <string name="idea">Share your AIR pollution control Ideas</string>


    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="co">co</string>
    <string name="textView4">>>"Good" AQI is 0 to 50. Air quality is considered satisfactory, and air pollution poses little or no risk.
    For example, people who are unusually sensitive to ozone may experience respiratory symptoms.                   </string>
    <string name="textView5">>>"Unhealthy for Sensitive Groups" AQI is 101 to 150. Although general public is not likely to be affected at this AQI range, people with lung disease, older adults and children are at a greater risk from exposure to ozone, whereas persons with heart and lung disease, older adults and children are at greater risk from the presence of particles in the air.                     </string>
    <string name="textView6">>>"Unhealthy" AQI is 151 to 200. Everyone may begin to experience some adverse health effects, and members of the sensitive groups may experience more serious effects.                            </string>
    <string name="textView7">>>"Very Unhealthy" AQI is 201 to 300. This would trigger a health alert signifying that everyone may experience more serious health effects.                                         </string>
    <string name="textView8">>>"Hazardous" AQI greater than 300. This would trigger a health warnings of emergency conditions. The entire population is more likely to be affected.                                                   </string>
    <string name="title_activity_city">City</string>
    <string name="city_label">View Pollution by City</string>
    <string name="aqi_title">AQI</string>
    <string name="textView9">>>>"At a domestic level, faulty gas appliances and cigarette smoking are significant sources of carbon monoxide. Natural processes produce relatively small amounts. Carbon monoxide reacts with other pollutants in the air to form potentially harmful ground level ozone. This occurs close to the site of emission"                      </string>
    <string name="textView10">>>>"These gases, especially SO2, are emitted by the burning of fossil fuels — coal, oil, and diesel — or other materials that contain sulfur. Sources include power plants, metals processing and smelting facilities, and vehicles."                  </string>
    <string name="textView11">>>"Nitrogen Dioxide (NO2) Pollution. NO2 primarily gets in the air from the burning of fuel. NO2 forms from emissions from cars, trucks and buses, power plants, and off-road equipment."              </string>
    <string name="textView12">>>"Particulate matter particles can either originate from antropogenic (caused by humans) or from natural sources. Volcanic eruptions, soil erosion, sea salt or the import of desert sand are all examples of possible sources of particulate matter."              </string>
    <string name="textView13">>>"Where Do PM2.5 Come From. Fine particles can come from various sources. They include power plants, motor vehicles, airplanes, residential wood burning, forest fires, agricultural burning, volcanic eruptions and dust storms."                          </string>
    <string name="place_holder">---</string>
    <string name="b1">view causes</string>
    <string name="textView14">>>>"People experience a wide range of health effects from being exposed to air pollution. Effects can be broken down into short-term effects and long-term effects .                                                         </string>
    <string name="textView15">>>>"Short-term effects, which are temporary, include illnesses such as pneumonia or bronchitis. They also include discomfort such as irritation to the nose, throat, eyes, or skin. Air pollution can also cause headaches, dizziness, and nausea. Bad smells made by factories, garbage, or sewer systems are considered air pollution, too. These odors are less serious but still unpleasant.view causes "                                      </string>
    <string name="textView16">>>>"Long-term effects of air pollution can last for years or for an entire lifetime. They can even lead to a persons death.Long-term health effects from air pollution include heart disease, lung cancer, and respiratory diseases such as emphysema. Air pollution can also cause long-term damage to peoples nerves, brain, kidneys, liver, and other organs. Some scientists suspect air pollutants cause birth defects. Nearly 2.5 million people die worldwide each year from the effects of outdoor or indoor air pollution."                                                                          </string>
    <string name="textView17">>>>"People react differently to different types of air pollution. Young children and older adults, whose immune systems tend to be weaker, are often more sensitive to pollution. Conditions such as asthma, heart disease, and lung disease can be made worse by exposure to air pollution. The length of exposure and amount and type of pollutants are also factors."                                    </string>
    <string name="textView18">view causes</string>
    <string name="b3">Effects</string>
    <string name="b2">view health condition</string>
    <string name="pressure">causes</string>
    <string name="humidity">condition</string>
    <string name="wind">Effects</string>
    <string name="attribution">Attributions</string>
    <string name="pollutants_aqi">Pollutants AQI</string>

    <!--AQI Scale-->
    <string name="good">Good</string>
    <string name="moderate">Moderate</string>
    <string name="unhealthy_for_sensitive">Unhealthy for Sensitive Group</string>
    <string name="unhealthy">Unhealthy</string>
    <string name="very_unhealthy">Very Unhealthy</string>
    <string name="hazardous">Hazardous</string>

    <!--Info Dialog-->

    <!--AQI Range-->
    <string name="good_range">0 – 50</string>
    <string name="moderate_range">51 – 100</string>
    <string name="unhealthy_for_sensitive_range">101 – 150</string>
    <string name="unhealthy_range">151 – 200</string>
    <string name="very_unhealthy_range">201 – 300</string>
    <string name="hazardous_range">300+</string>

    <!--Health Implications-->
    <string name="good_health_implications">Air quality is considered satisfactory, and air pollution poses little or no risk.                                           </string>
    <string name="moderate_health_implications">Air quality is acceptable; however, for some pollutants there may be a moderate health concern for a very small number of people who are unusually sensitive to air pollution.                        </string>
    <string name="unhealthy_for_sensitive_health_implications">Members of sensitive groups may experience health effects. The general public is not likely to be affected.                                     </string>
    <string name="unhealthy_health_implications">Everyone may begin to experience health effects; members of sensitive groups may experience more serious health effects.                                        </string>
    <string name="very_unhealthy_health_implications">Health warnings of emergency conditions. The entire population is more likely to be affected.                                                               </string>
    <string name="hazardous_health_implications">Health alert: everyone may experience more serious health effects.                                                                                </string>

    <string name="appwidget_text">AQI</string>
    <string name="add_widget">Add widget</string>

    <string name="shareText">Hey, Check the Air Quality in your area with this app: https://pollutionmonitor.page.link/RtQw</string>


    <string name="temperature_unit_celsius">%1$.1f &#176;C</string>
    <string name="humidity_unit">%1$.0f%%</string>
    <string name="pressureplace_holder_unit">%1$.1f mb</string>
    <string name="wind_unit">%1$.1f m/s</string>
    <string name="textview5" />
    <string name="select_city">Select City</string>
    <string name="button">search</string>
    <string name="tx1">City</string>
    <string name="tx2">Assign Job</string>
    <string name="txt3">Activity</string>
    <string name="bt2">save</string>
    <string name="bt3">Load</string>


    <string name="recycler_view">Causes</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string-array name="gases">
        <item>CARBON DIOXIDE</item>
        <item>NITROUS OXIDE</item>
        <item>OZONE</item>
        <item>PM 2.5</item>
        <item>PM 10</item>
        <item>SULFUR DIOXIDE</item>
        <item>CONCLUSION</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="causes">
        <item>>>>>"At a domestic level, faulty gas appliances and cigarette smoking are significant sources of carbon monoxide. Natural processes produce relatively small amounts. Carbon monoxide reacts with other pollutants in the air to form potentially harmful ground level ozone. This occurs close to the site of emission"   </item>
        <item>>>>"Nitrogen Dioxide (NO2) Pollution. NO2 primarily gets in the air from the burning of fuel. NO2 forms from emissions from cars, trucks and buses, power plants, and off-road equipment."  </item>
        <item> >>>>"In the Earth's lower atmosphere, near ground level, ozone is formed when pollutants emitted by cars, power plants, industrial boilers, refineries, chemical plants, and other sources react chemically in the presence of sunlight. Ozone at ground level is a harmful air pollutant."</item>
        <item> >>>"Where Do PM2.5 Come From. Fine particles can come from various sources. They include power plants, motor vehicles, airplanes, residential wood burning, forest fires, agricultural burning, volcanic eruptions and dust storms."  </item>
        <item> >>>"Particulate matter particles can either originate from antropogenic (caused by humans) or from natural sources. Volcanic eruptions, soil erosion, sea salt or the import of desert sand are all examples of possible sources of particulate matter."  </item>
        <item>>>>>"It is formed when fuel containing sulfur, such as coal and oil, is burned, creating air pollution. Most sulfur dioxide air pollution comes from the burning of coal and oil in power plants. It is also emitted by trains, large ships, and some diesel equipment that burns high sulfur fuel, and by volcanic eruptions."</item>
        <item>>>>>"In many countries heart disease is a leading cause of death and even a small contribution from air pollution could mean a significant and important effect on public heath. On an individual level, the risk to health from air pollution is very much smaller than that posed by active cigarette smoking or accidents"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="health">
        <item>..>>>>When you have too much carbon dioxide in blood for several days or weeks, the condition is known as chronic hypercapnia. This can happen due to diseases like emphysema, in which the lungs are incapable of adequate gas exchange.</item>
        <item>...>>>he main effect of breathing in raised levels of nitrogen dioxide is the increased likelihood of respiratory problems. Nitrogen dioxide inflames the lining of the lungs, and it can reduce immunity to lung infections. This can cause problems such as wheezing, coughing, colds, flu and bronchitis.</item>
        <item>....>>>>Ozone is a powerful oxidant that can irritate the airways. Ozone in the air we breathe can harm our health, especially on hot sunny days when ozone can reach unhealthy levels. Even relatively low levels of ozone can cause health effects.</item>
        <item>....>>>>Long-term exposure to ambient particulate matter with aerodynamic diameter 2.5 µm (referred to as PM2.5) has potential health risks due to cardiovascular and respiratory diseases leading to premature mortality</item>
        <item>....>>>he size of particles is directly linked to their potential for causing health problems. Small particles less than 10 micrometers in diameter pose the greatest problems, because they can get deep into your lungs, and some may even get into your bloodstream. 1. premature death in people with heart or lung disease 2. nonfatal heart attacks 3. irregular heartbeat 4. aggravated asthma 5. decreased lung function 6. increased respiratory symptoms</item>
        <item>.>>>>>>>Sulfur dioxide (SO 2) is a colorless, reactive air pollutant with a strong odor. This gas can be a threat to human health, animal health, and plant life. The main sources of sulfur dioxide emissions are from fossil fuel combustion and natural volcanic activity.</item>
        <item>.....>>>>>Air pollution can severely impact health, and can lead to premature death since it reduces lung function, increases infection and cancer risk, and worsens health in those with heart or lung disease.....</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>
